[{"answer": "Well tonight, Piers, things have really come down.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "What would you describe the mood tonight?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "Hi, Piers.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "Jesse, how are you?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "Good.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 54, "question": "How are you doing tonight?", "qSentId": 53}, {"answer": "Well, yes.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "There's a huge disconnect, isn't there now, between the two?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "Well, the fact that the Democrats and Republicans, and both of them are equally guilty.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 77, "question": "What has gone fundamentally wrong with America to cause what is going on now at Wall Street and other cities?", "qSentId": 76}, {"answer": "Well, there's only one person that I like at all of them.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "Who don't you like?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "I mean, Ron Paul is unlikely the way the polls are looking to win.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "Can you imagine the money we could put forward to our infrastructure if we weren't involved in these two stupid wars that we've been in for 10 years?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "Well, Newt Gingrich, it's interesting.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 122, "question": "What do you think of the rest of the field?", "qSentId": 121}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "Would you agree if the CIA discovered tomorrow that they knew where Osama bin Laden was that he should be assassinated?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "What about Gadhafi?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "You don't care?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "Isn't that --", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "We just go out, and if people we don't like, we kill them?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "Jesse, with respect.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 150, "question": "Everyone is willing to be killed?", "qSentId": 149}, {"answer": "No, when in war.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "Isn't that exactly what Navy SEALs do all the time?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "Well, let me ask you a direct question.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 189, "question": "How do I know they're telling me the truth?", "qSentId": 188}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "Do you believe bin Laden is dead?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "Because --", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 212, "question": "How do we know?", "qSentId": 211}, {"answer": "What troubled me about it was our media here.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 218, "question": "What was your view of Gadhafi being taken out in public in the way that he was?", "qSentId": 217}, {"answer": "Well, I will vote absolutely for Ron Paul if he -- if he runs as an independent.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "Have you decided yet?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "Well, let's talk about your wealth first.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 275, "question": "Would you feel comfortable discussing that?", "qSentId": 274}, {"answer": "Well, it's actually $25 million.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 280, "question": "stroke NBC $24 million?", "qSentId": 279}, {"answer": "I'm not the queen of television.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 288, "question": "You're the queen of television, aren't you?", "qSentId": 287}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "And you've parted company with Andre, your boyfriend of some time, this year?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "I can't speak about that publicly out of a personal request.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 302, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 301}, {"answer": "Because, you know, I just -- I made a promise to someone, so I like to be a man of my word.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "Why leave him out of it?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "I don't remember.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "But it was your decision?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "You don't remember?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "It was almost three weeks ago.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "You can't remember whose decision it was?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "I'm happy to -- I mean I'm just happy.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "Are you enjoying being single again?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "Are you on the prowl?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "I like -- I don't know, I like to be challenged.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "What do you like about them?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "I just heard of it.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 353, "question": "What do you think of the Demi-Ashton split today?", "qSentId": 352}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "Well, you just told me about it backstage, right?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "Well, yes, I think they probably had a lot of good times with some other women and then --", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "You think so?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "Well, come on.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "How do you know this?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "The lines of cocaine on the table.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "What lines?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "Mm-hmm.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "Is this true?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "Let's -- yes, lets show some little clip of what they said about the marriage.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "Together?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "And they seemed -- I mean, to me, they seemed very much in love at the time.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "Was it?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "Do you tolerate infidelity yourself?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "ORGAN: Good.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "How is he doing?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "Probably not.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "I've never come close to marriage.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 446, "question": "What was the closest you came?", "qSentId": 445}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "Because I know you kind of fancy yourself on politics, are you?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "The chances are you probably will.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 476, "question": "Is he right?", "qSentId": 475}, {"answer": "We are just very competitive over everything.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "What happened?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "ANDLER: Oh, because all of all your reality world?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 505, "question": "The political landscape?", "qSentId": 504}, {"answer": "Let's start with Republicans.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "Well, where shall we start?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "Well, I --", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "What do we make of Herman Cain?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "Well, I think the whole point now in politics is to kind of get yourself out there.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 513, "question": "He's engaging, isn't he?", "qSentId": 512}, {"answer": "But no, no, I firmly believe that people like Herman Cain and Michele Bachmann, and -- I think that they all really -- I mean Ron Paul, probably not.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "I think that's what he's up to, isn't it?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "He didn't seem to know what Libya was.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 522, "question": "Did you see the video of him when they asked about Libya and Obama?", "qSentId": 521}, {"answer": "Well, let me tell you why.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "ORGAN: Why don't you go into politics?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "I am a Brit.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 552, "question": "Are you British?", "qSentId": 551}, {"answer": "No, you don't.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 555, "question": "I beg your pardon?", "qSentId": 554}, {"answer": "I'm flushing.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 651, "question": "You are, I think the word is flushing, aren't you?", "qSentId": 650}, {"answer": "Yes, flushing and blushing.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 658, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 657}, {"answer": "He was just much older.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 685, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 684}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 691, "question": "You want to pay more tax?", "qSentId": 690}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 724, "question": "The government?", "qSentId": 723}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 726, "question": "Where are you supposed to write the check to?", "qSentId": 725}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 760, "question": "Do you not watch any news?", "qSentId": 759}, {"answer": "Well, It wouldn't make any sense.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 778, "question": "Wouldn't that be cool?", "qSentId": 777}, {"answer": "Well, that's one version of what happened.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 784, "question": "Because you were staying in the break how, under different circumstances, you'd go for me?", "qSentId": 783}, {"answer": "They got him back for the third year, despite all the anger last year.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 803, "question": "No, when did that happen?", "qSentId": 802}, {"answer": "I hope so.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 807, "question": "Is Hollywood beginning to understand that kind of humor?", "qSentId": 806}, {"answer": "Yes, but I think it's been getting worse.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 813, "question": "Wasn't it two years ago?", "qSentId": 812}, {"answer": "Well, I believe it is.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 817, "question": "It's about stop taking yourself too seriously, isn't it?", "qSentId": 816}, {"answer": "I hope there are more cutaways to all their faces when he -- when I had Ricky on the show just after the Globes last year, it was brilliant, because when I played back the stuff to him, he never laughed at the punch line.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 823, "question": "Is that what we're worried about?", "qSentId": 822}, {"answer": "It can be.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 841, "question": "Historic?", "qSentId": 840}, {"answer": "Anyone.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 843, "question": "About who?", "qSentId": 842}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 845, "question": "50 Cent?", "qSentId": 844}, {"answer": "Because I'm speaking now.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 876, "question": "Why are you repeating what I said?", "qSentId": 875}, {"answer": "Keep the shameless plugs down to a minimum.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 882, "question": "Are you a listener?", "qSentId": 881}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 889, "question": "Don't you have a baby on the way?", "qSentId": 888}, {"answer": "No, I wouldn't, because I protect my own privacy unlike you American celebrities.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 891, "question": "Wouldn't you plug that baby, if you could?", "qSentId": 890}, {"answer": "First of all, you have a new show every day, just like I do.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 901, "question": "How do you want this interview to be remembered?", "qSentId": 900}, {"answer": "It's a bit like that.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 908, "question": "Oh, this is like Nixon/Frost?", "qSentId": 907}, {"answer": "You have a chubby face.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 921, "question": "Because everyone is just banging on about this?", "qSentId": 920}, {"answer": "Well rounded, well fed, we would say in England.", "docId": "111117pmt", "aSentId": 925, "question": "What would you call it?", "qSentId": 924}]